intouchgossip.com 2013-08-05

# Privacy Policy | In Touch Gossip

### intouchgossip.com Privacy Policy

We know that safeguarding your privacy is serious business. Your privacy is very important to us. Please take a moment to read this privacy policy so that you understand how we collect, use and disclose information about you. As we update and expand our services, this policy might change, so please check it out from time to time. If we update this privacy policy, the “last updated” line above will be revised. If you have questions about our privacy policy, please e-mail us at [privacypolicy@bauerpublishing.com](mailto:privacypolicy@bauerpublishing.com)

 **Your continued use of intouchgossip.com (the “Website”) or submission of any information to us is consent to this Privacy Policy and the intouchgossip.com Terms of Use. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not use our website.**

### Your California Privacy Rights

Pursuant to California Civil Code Section 1798.83, you may request the following information, which will be provided to you via either a writing or e-mail free of charge: (1) a list of the categories of personal information disclosed by intouchgossip.com to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding calendar year and (2) the names and addresses of all third parties that received personal information from intouchgossip.com for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year and, if the nature of the third parties’ business cannot reasonably be determined from the third parties’ name, examples of the products or services marketed, if known to intouchgossip.com, sufficient to give you a reasonable indication of the nature of the third parties’ business.

Consumer requests for this information should be sent to [privacypolicy@bauerpublishing.com](mailto:privacypolicy@bauerpublishing.com).

### What types of personal information does intouchgossip.com collect?

We may collect Personal Information from you when you sign up for services at intouchgossip.com, enter contests or sweepstakes, contact us via e-mail, and in other instances where you provide us with personal information. Personal Information includes data such as your first and last name, residence address, telephone number, e-mail address, or any other information that would allow someone to identify you.

Some examples where you provide Personal Information to us include:

  1. If you subscribe to a free newsletter or to receive notification of special offers from intouchgossip.com;
  2. If you enter contests or sweepstakes sponsored by intouchgossip.com or featured on our Website; or
  3. If you respond to surveys.

### What is intouchgossip.com's policy for children under the age of 13?

intouchgossip.com is not intended for children’s use. If you are under the age of 13, please exit this Website and do not provide us with any Personal Information. intouchgossip.com does not knowingly accept collect Personal Information from children under 13, as doing so is restricted by the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA"). For more information on COPPA, please refer to the Federal Trade Commission website.

### How does intouchgossip.com use this Personal Information?

Personal Information may be used for marketing and promotional purposes by intouchgossip.com and its parent companies, subsidiaries and affiliates. We also may rent, sell or otherwise disclose your Personal Information to advertisers, sponsors, business partners and other third parties for their use.

### Third-party Agents

We occasionally have third party agents and partners that perform functions on our behalf, such as marketing, analytics, or fraud protection. These entities have access to the Personal Information needed to perform their functions and are contractually obligated to maintain the confidentiality and security of that personal information.

### Emergency Situations

We may also use or disclose Personal Information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to applicable law or comply with legal process served on intouchgossip.com; (b) protect and defend our rights or property, the Website or our users; (c) enforce the Website’s Terms of Use; and (d) act under emergency circumstances to protect the personal safety of us, our affiliates, agents, or the users of the Website or the public.

### Does intouchgossip.com collect non-personal information?

intouchgossip.com also collects anonymous information about your navigation of our Website, as described below.

### What are cookies and how does intouchgossip.com use them?

Cookies are small pieces of data that are placed on your computer's hard drive when you visit intouchgossip.com. Cookies are standard in the industry; you'll find them at most major websites. Cookies allow intouchgossip.com to keep track of which areas of our site you have visited, how long you spend on a particular page and sites that have referred you to intouchgossip.com, to track your preferences and interests, and to personalize your experience at intouchgossip.com.

### What is an IP address and how does intouchgossip.com use it?

An IP address is a number that's automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're surfing the web - your computer's unique "signature." Web servers automatically identify your computer by its IP address. When you visit intouchgossip.com, we collect some general information about your computer, including its IP address, the operating system it uses (for example, Windows XP), the browser software it uses (for example, Microsoft Internet Explorer), and your Internet service provider (for example, AOL). This information helps us better understand the people who visit intouchgossip.com.

intouchgossip.com collects this general information to identify the most popular areas on our website and to provide aggregate information to our advertisers to let them know about the number of people who have seen and clicked on their advertisements.

### What are web beacons and how does intouchgossip.com use them?

intouchgossip.com may contain tiny electronic images known as web beacons. We may use web beacons to assist us in delivering cookies on the Website and to allow us to count users who have visited those pages. We may include web beacons in promotional email messages to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon.

### Use of non-personal Information

We may share statistical or aggregated non-personal information about our users with advertisers, business partners, sponsors and other third parties. This data is used to customize our Website content and advertising to deliver a better experience to our users.

We may work with third-party advertising companies who may utilize cookies and web beacons, and data collected on this site, to customize advertisements to you on this, as well as on other websites in their networks beyond this website. These companies do not have access to or use your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number or other personally identifiable information; they may, however, anonymously track your Internet usage across this and other websites in their networks. For more information about these advertising companies' privacy policies, including how to opt out from their use of cookies and web beacons to track your use of websites, see [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

### What happens when I link to or from another website?

You should also be aware that other companies may advertise on our site, and intouchgossip.com may provide links to other websites. These advertisers and sites may collect data or solicit personal information from you. intouchgossip.com does not control these advertisers and sites, and this Privacy Policy does not address the practices of these other companies and sites. We are not responsible for the actions and privacy policies of third parties and other websites. We encourage you to be aware of when you leave intouchgossip.com and to read the privacy policy of each website that you visit.

### How does intouchgossip.com protect my Personal Information?

We strive to ensure that your information is secure on our system. Only those employees who need access to your information in order to do their jobs are allowed access. intouchgossip.com sometimes asks for your credit card information in order to provide you with goods or services that you request. This information is securely stored on our computers (also called "servers"). While we use all reasonable efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your information, we will have no liability for disclosure of any information obtained due to errors in transmission or the unauthorized acts of third parties. No data storage system or transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us. You do so at your own risk.

### Governing Law/Assignment

intouchgossip.com is published in the United States and is intended for users from the United States. U.S. law will govern in any and all disputes, including privacy or defamation issues or otherwise.

We may change our ownership or corporate organization while providing the Website. As a result, please be aware that we may transfer your information to another company with which we have merged. Under such circumstances to the extent possible intouchgossip.com would require the acquiring party to follow the practices described in this privacy policy, as it may be amended from time to time.

### Will intouchgossip.com update this policy?

We also reserve the right to change or update this policy, or any other policy or practice, at any time, with reasonable notice to users of this Website.

### How can you correct or update your Personal Information?

If you would like to correct or update Personal Information you previously provided to intouchgossip.com, you can let us know by sending us an e-mail at [privacypolicy@bauerpublishing.com](mailto:privacypolicy@bauerpublishing.com) or mailing a letter to our postal address listed below.

### How can you contact intouchgossip.com?

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, you can contact us at:

> In Touch Gossip  
> 270 Sylvan Avenue  
> Englewood Cliffs, NJ 07632  
> (201) 569-6699
